JOACHIM HODANA

JUNIOR PYTHON DEVELOPER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Bydgoszcz/Remote Poland

EMAIL

me@joachimhodana.com

LINKS

github.com/style77 joachimhodana.com

SKILLS

Python

React, Vite, Next.js

Typescript, Javascript

Docker, Git

SQL, NoSQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Django, DRF, FastAPI

Celery, RabbitMQ

CI/CD, Unit/integration tests

LANGUAGES

Polish

• • • • •

English

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

PROFILE

As a passionate developer who began coding at 13, I am quickly grasping new technologies and frameworks. With experience in frontend technologies like Vite, React, and Next, I prefer backend development, focusing on Python and Go. I am open to relocating to Warsaw after my high school exam, if desired by an employer.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Python Developer, Decision Sciences AI

Remote

Nov 2022 — May 2023

Created data analysis pipelines for insurance prices prediction software using Python & data tools. Extracted, cleaned & analyzed data to derive valuable insights, improving efficiency & risk assessment. Used Pandas, Numpy & Postgresql.

Freelancer

Oct 2022 — Present

Used web technologies, Python, a bit of PHP, and a lot more to deliver products for clients. Developed many websites, APIs and worked with teams to deliver apps with great code quality

EDUCATION

Teleinformatics Technician, Zespół Szkół Elektronicznych

Bydgoszcz

Oct 2019 — Apr 2024

PROJECTS

Skynotes

Dec 2023 — Present

Cloud storage developed using DRF and React, integrating microservices through gRPC, such as a thumbnailer - a service for creating thumbnails for files written in Go. Utilized Celery with RabbitMQ and custom EventBus for file handling. All of that stacked in one docker-compose for easy one-click deployment.

code: github.com/style77/skynotes

Quantex

Jul 2023

Powerful trading bot with ChatGPT sentiment analysis of news headlines. Inspired by a paper released by Alejandro Lopez-Lira and Yuehua Tang from the University of Florida. Used FastAPI to create an API for storing all the data for future use and connected a Telegram bot to automatically send the analysis.

code: github.com/style77/quantex

Streamx

Jun 2023 — Jul 2023

Live streaming platform written in Django, Next.js with use of Nginx-rtmp module to forward HLS streams - Includes validation with stream keys and allows users to stream from OBS Studio.

code: github.com/style77/streamx

REFERENCES

Marek Balcerzak from Decision Sciences Al

marek.balcerzak@decisionsciences.ai

INTERNSHIPS

Network Engineer internship, LOGON S.A.

Bydgoszcz

Jan 2022 — Feb 2022

School internship, I were responsible for creating networks around the office to learn how they work. I also worked with IP cameras and other network-related devices.

Helpdesk & PHP developer, Zakład Informatyki Stosowanej

Bydgoszcz

May 2023 — Jun 2023

Developed a customized ticket report user interface (UI) using PHP – it was my initial experience with the language. I used to visit clients to handle hardware and software repairs provided by the company.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the European Union's General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Data Protection Act. I am aware that I have the right to withdraw my consent at any time.